What did I see today while trying to hide from my husband and Rama?
So my husband and my son Rama together would make
me do so much work every day.   Let me
live, let me live.
Sometimes they say, take this and catch Rama.   Have
you seen my slippers?  Feed Rama.
I have gone crazy because of all these actions of his.
And that's why today I
thought that I should take revenge from both of them.  And
after some time I told them that let's
play a game today in which I will hide
and both of you will find me
but there is one condition, I will
hide first and till then you guys count.
One two three
and today I will hide in such a place that these people will
not be able to find me in this life.
[Music]
Hey friend, where should I hide? I could hide in this room,
but it's so dark in here.  Let's
hide in this room but we could
n't find any space here.  Let's do one thing, let's
hide under this blanket.  These people will
never be able to find me.
DAD [SCREAMING]
[MUSIC]
Hey, where did your mommy go?  What should I
do now?  Hey, what happened that it is so late
but these people have not been able to find me yet
and in this heat,
I am drenched in sweat under the blanket and
poor my husband and my son, now
I feel bad for them that maybe
they are crying because I was not found.
Stop playing all this hide and seek.  I will go and
see what these people are doing.
What have these people done?  [music]
A fat elephant